var questions = [{
    question: '1) The Braavos saying "Valar Morghulis" translates to...',
    choices: ["a) All men must serve", "b) Praise the Many Faced God", "c) All men must die", "d) Praise the Braavosi"],
    correctAnswer: "c) All men must die",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "images/valar-morhulis-gif.webp",
},
{
    question: "2) Who was responsible for the death of Robb and Catelyn Stark?",
    choices: ["a) The Lannisters", "b) The Greyjoys", "c) The Baratheons", "d) The Freys"],
    correctAnswer: "d) The Freys",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "assets/images/frey.gif",
},
{
    question: "3) Which of the following is not part of Daenerys Targaryen's full title?",
    choices: ["a) The Silver-haired", "b) The Mother of Dragons", "c) The Breaker of Chains", "d) The Queen of the Andals"],
    correctAnswer: "a) The Silver-haired",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "assets/images/daenerys.gif",
},
{
    question: "4) After traveling North of the Wall, Brandon Stark becomes ...",
    choices: ["a) Bran the Broken", "b) A Whitewalker ", "c) The Three-Eyed Raven", "d) One of the Free Folk"],
    correctAnswer: "c) The Three-Eyed Raven",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "../images/bran-stark.gif",
},
{
    question: "5) What discovery does Samwell Tarly make while at the Citadel?",
    choices: ["a) Jaime Lannister fathered Cersei's children", "b) Jon Snow's true parents are Lyanna Stark and Rhaegar Targaryen", "c) Tyrion Lannister murdered his father", "d) Cersei Lannister used wildfire to destroy the Sept of Baelor"],
    correctAnswer: "b) Jon Snow's true parents are Lyanna Stark and Rhaegar Targaryen",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
},
{
    question: "6) Who did Arya Stark train to serve?",
    choices: ["a) The Lord of Light", "b) The New Gods - The Seven ", "c) The Horse God", "d) The Many-Faced God"],
    correctAnswer: "d) The Many-Faced God",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
},
{
    question: "7) Who is Roberty Baratheon's last heir?",
    choices: ["a) Tommen", "b) Joffrey", "c) Gendry", "d) Myrcella"],
    correctAnswer: "c) Gendry",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
},
{
    question: "8) At the end of the series, the rightful leader in the North is...",
    choices: ["a) Jon Snow", "b) Sansa Stark", "c) Daenerys Targaryen", "d) Brandon Stark"],
    correctAnswer: "b) Sansa Stark",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
},
{
    question: "9) Who defeated the Night King?",
    choices: ["a) Arya Stark", "b) Jon Snow", "c) Daenerys Targaryen", "d) Brandon Stark"],
    correctAnswer: "a) Arya Stark",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
},
{
    question: '10) Complete this famous line: "When you play the Game of Thrones..."',
    choices: ["a) you fly, or you fry.", "b) everyone is your enemy.", "c) you answer to no one.", "d) you win, or you die."],
    correctAnswer: "d) you win, or you die.",
    correctAnswerGifUrl: "",
}
]
